[{"question":"SQA stands for:","answer":"a","optionC":"Simple Quotua Analysic","optionD":"None of the above","optionA":"Software Quality Assurance","optionB":"SQL Analysic"},{"question":"Which planet has the Longest day among all planets in the solar \nsystem?","answer":"c","optionC":"  Venus","optionD":"  Jupiter","optionA":"  Neptune ","optionB":"  Saturn "},{"question":"   Which is the smallest Continent in the world??","answer":"b","optionC":"  AUSTRALIA","optionD":"  ARCTIC","optionA":"  ASIA","optionB":"  AFRICA"},{"question":"In which of these two Sports is the term 'Free Hit' used??","answer":"d","optionC":"Badminton , Cricket","optionD":"Hockey , Cricket","optionA":"Football , Squash","optionB":"Badminton , Tennis"},{"question":"According to the 2011 census which of these states enjoys a literacy \nrate of over 90%?","answer":"b","optionC":"  Tripura","optionD":"  Gujarat","optionA":"  Punjab","optionB":"  Mizoram"},{"question":"Which team has Won Most ICC Trophies????","answer":"b","optionC":"  Pakistan","optionD":"  England","optionA":"  India","optionB":"  Australia"},{"question":"The First Nobel Prize in physics was awarded for the discovery of what?","answer":"c","optionC":"  X-Ray","optionD":"  Vaccum Tubes","optionA":"  Laser","optionB":"  Transistor"},{"question":"Which  team has won most number of IPL Trophies??","answer":"b","optionC":"RCB","optionD":"SRH","optionA":"CSK","optionB":"MI"},{"question":"Which Cricketer has scored 10000 runs in both tests and ODIs and \ntaken more than 500 Wickets in international cricket?","answer":"d","optionC":"  Sanath Jayasuriya","optionD":"  Jacques Kallis ","optionA":"  Saurav Ganguly","optionB":"  Sachin Tendulkar"},{"question":"Which is the Largest Lok Sabha constituency in the country in terms of\narea?","answer":"c","optionC":"  Ladakh","optionD":"  Sikkim","optionA":"  Barmer , Rajasthan","optionB":"  South Goa "},{"question":"     Which is the Largest Cricket Stadium  in the World??","answer":"b","optionC":"Edens Gardens","optionD":"Holkar stadium","optionA":"Melbourne Cricket Ground","optionB":"Narendra Modi Stadium"},{"question":"Which Sports will be played in the proposed Indian Super league?","answer":"a","optionC":"  Badminton","optionD":"  Cricket","optionA":"  Football","optionB":"  Tennis"},{"question":"In Sholay,Whom did Gabbar ask Kitna inaam rakhi hai sarkaar hum par?","answer":"a","optionC":"  Kaalia","optionD":"  Thakur","optionA":"  Samba","optionB":"  Veeru"},{"question":"  The Language of Lakshadweep , a Union Territory of India , is","answer":"c","optionC":" Malayalam","optionD":" Telugu","optionA":" Tamil","optionB":" Hindi"},{"question":"  What do the five rings of the Olympics represent??","answer":"c","optionC":"  Five Continents","optionD":"  Five Oceans","optionA":"  Five Games","optionB":"  Five Languages"},{"question":"  In India by whom the budget  passed first ?","answer":"b","optionC":" Both A&B","optionD":" None of these","optionA":" Rajya Sabha ","optionB":" Lok Sabha "},{"question":"Dr. Rajendra Prasad was elected as the first President of India ?","answer":"d","optionC":" By the people of India ","optionD":" By the Constituency Assembly ","optionA":" Parliament ","optionB":" By the electoral college "},{"question":" According to the Indian Constitution, who is the first citizen of India ?","answer":"b","optionC":"  Vice President ","optionD":" Lok Sabha Speaker ","optionA":"  Prime Minister","optionB":"  President  "}]